500 brownies delivered in less than 24 hours
9 point of sale
and you must think I'm flying,
man
then that you are wrong
after 1 beautiful walk
I'm arriving at another 1 point of sale
here from Charlie Brown
c
think that's how it is bro
put the product on the guys shelf
just get the money and that's it
already made money
it's not just putting it at points of sale
think you're winning
pop and such
one if the guy doesn't sell bro
he won't buy from you anymore
and then everything I'm building here
turns into a sand castle
the bro goes there
bought the first
did not buy the second
there is no recurrence
turned on
don't you think everything is won
go to that brother
foot on the ground
slowly
understanding that it's happening
but you haven't gained anything
it's the first skateboard store we've been to
you're here exchanging an idea that makes a lot of sense
the brand skateboard
worth my bro
tamo together
mark the store there if you can
like a rent
bro you're using the guy's space
to promote your brand
so you gotta do the run
not him
you don't move brother
don't wait for the guy to move for you no bro
IF i Find out you can move
and then brother
you also already have the eye of an,
right kid
if I don't go where I go
in 1 week these points of sale
0 hand looks like 1 sand castle
is on
pay attention
the guys can give you the shelf
but you are the one who needs to create demand
mwezi WA tattoo